Paul Abelson Papers 5192
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Jan to July
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Aug to Dec
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Jan to April
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  May to Dec
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  Jan to March
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  April to Dec
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Jan. to June
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  July to Dec.
- Correspondence, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  Jan. to Feb.
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Clippings, broadsides, miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Agreements, 1912-1924 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1925-1931 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  plus undated
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Agreements, 1932-1942 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Minutes of the Conference Between Representative of the Manufacturers Association's of the Fur Industry and Representatives of the Furriers' Union of Greater II and Vicinity of the AFL, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Sept to Oct.
- Minutes of the Conference Between Representative of the Manufacturers Association's of the Fur Industry and Representatives of the Furriers' Union of Greater II and Vicinity of the AFL, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Minutes of the Conference Between Representative of the Manufacturers Association's of the Fur Industry and Representatives of the Furriers' Union of Greater II and Vicinity of the AFL, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Minutes of the Conference Between Representative of the Manufacturers Association's of the Fur Industry and Representatives of the Furriers' Union of Greater II and Vicinity of the AFL, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Conference Held Between the Board of Arbitration and Conciliation, as. Established by the Contract Entered Into, Between the Association Employers of Fur Workers Inc. and the International Union of Fur Workers of the U.S., 1919 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Conference Held Between the Board of Arbitration and Conciliation, as. Established by the Contract Entered Into, Between the Association Employers of Fur Workers Inc. and the International Union of Fur Workers of the U.S., 1919 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Report of Conference Between Employers Representing Union Shops, and Employees Representatives of International Fur Workers Union of the U.S., Locals 2 & 3, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  January
- Minutes, Fur Dressers and Dyers, Fleshers and Floor Workers, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Minutes, Fur Dressers and Dyers, Fleshers and Floor Workers, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Minutes of Meeting of Committees Representing Fur Dressers' and Fur Dyers' Association, As Employers, and Locals 2 and 3 of the International Fur Workers Union, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Minutes of Meeting of Committees Representing Fur Dressers' and Fur Dyers' Association, As Employers, and Locals 2 and 3 of the International Fur Workers Union, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Report of the General Executive Board, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, notes, minutes re Security Fund, 1927-1931 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Propper Handbag Co. vs. LHPNW, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- E.M. Kay Ladies Handbag Co. vs. LHPNW, Local 1, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Thompson Art Mirror Co. vs. LHPNW, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Binnen Davis Co. vs. LHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Association of I.I. Handbag Manufacturers vs. LHPNW, Local 1, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Centre Mirror Works vs. Novelty Mirror Workers Union, Local 7, LHPNW, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Emes Ideal Leather Belt Co., Inc. vs. International Pocketbook Workers Union, Local 1, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Centre Mirror Works vs. Novelty Mirror Workers Local 7, International Ladies Handbag, Pocket-book and Novelty Workers (LHPNW), 1937 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Herman Bag Co. vs. LHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Hat Lewis Purses, Inc. vs. LHPNW, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- I.I. Industrial Council of the National Authority for the Ladies' Handbag Industry vs. Pocketbook Workers Union of NY (PNW), 1944 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Mercury Sandbags vs. PWU, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Harold & Harold vs. PWU, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Coronet, Inc. vs. PWU, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Dauphin, Inc. vs. PWU, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. FWU, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Townly Handbag, Inc. vs. PWU, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Delle Handbags vs. PWU, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- A.J. Sirus Products Co. vs. PWU, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Clareen Handbags vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Dofan Handbags vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Glen Handbags vs PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Duetz vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Metro Handbags vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Salkay Handbags vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- I.J. Vogel & Co. vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Senco Leather Manufacturers vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Ritter & Ritter vs. PWU, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Henry Rosenfeld Inc. vs. PWU, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Lujean Bag Co. vs. PWU, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Grossbeck Leather Goods vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- A.L. Seamon vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Empire Products vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Kaplan and Gordon Corp. vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Jana Bags vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Princess Handbags vs. PWU, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Ambassador Handbag Co. vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Lesco Inc. vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Marmac Co. Inc. vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Weeda Handbag vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Capri Handbags vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Theo Rendl Inc. vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- F. Milch vs. PWU, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Koret Inc. vs. PWU, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Glen Handbags vs. PWU, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Calem Handbags vs. PWU, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Steinman Brothers vs. FWU, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Companion Bags vs. PWU, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Decisions, 1930-1936 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Cloth, Hat and Cap Manufacturers Association vs. Jt. Council of N.Y. of the United Cloth Hat and Capmakers of North America (UCHG), 1921 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  May
- American Headwear vs. UCHC, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  Oct
- Levinson Hat Co. vs. UCHC, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Klein, Frankfeldt & Aranoff vs. UCHC, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  Feb
- Selkin Brothers vs. UCHC, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  Dec
- Square Hat Co. vs. UCHC, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Perfect Cap Co. vs. UCHC, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  Jan
- Wholesale Hat & Cap Manufacturers vs. UCHC, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  Feb to Dec
- Excelsior Head-wear vs. UCHC, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Julius Levin & Co. vs. UCHC, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  July
- Central Cap Co. vs. UCHC, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Washington Hat Co. vs. United Hatters of America, Local 18, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  August
- Bernard Greenberg & Co. vs. UHCMW, Local 1, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  May to June
- Eastern Women's Head-wear Association vs. United Hatters, Cap & Millinery Workers International Union (UHCMW), 1935 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  Sept
- Men's Hat Lining Industry vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Dan-bury Hat Industry vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  Nov
- Allied Hat Manufacturers vs. UHCMW, Locals 7 & 8, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Paul Martin Hat Co., George McLachlan, Mallory Hat Co., Wilson Hat Co., Trimpsen Rough Hat Co., Beaver-Goodman Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, Locals 1 and 10 of Danbury, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Danbury Hatters vs. UHCMW, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  Aug to Oct
- Trimpsen Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  Sept to Nov
- Bernard Greenberg vs. UHCMW, Men's Hat Industry vs. UHCMW, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  May to July
- Manson Hat Co. vs. UHCMW, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Allied Hat Manufacturers vs. UHCMW, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Ruffelt Hat Go. vs. UHCMW, Local 94, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Merrimac Hat Corp. vs. UHCMW, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Style Park Hats, Inc. vs. UHCMW, Local 60, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Beatty Page vs. UHCMW, Local 80, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  June
- John B. Stetson Co. vs. UHCMW, Local 60, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Merrimac Hat Corp. vs. UHCMW, Local 87, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Style Park Hats vs. UHCMW, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Hat Leather Association vs. UHCMW, Local 70, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- John B. Stetson vs. UHCMW, Local 60, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1916-1929 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Misc. (Box 40, Folder 21)
- H.C. Aberle Co., Inc., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Index of Decisions, Full-Fashioned Hosiery Industry, 1929-1931 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Decisions, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Sept to July
- Holeproof Hosiery Co. vs. AFFFHW, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Holeproof Hosiery Co. of Milwaukee vs. American Federation of Full-Fashioned Hosiery Workers (AFFFHW), Branch No. 16, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Lehigh Silk Hosiery Mills vs. AFFFHW, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Decisions, Series B, 1930-1931 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Decisions, Series Cs, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  March to August
- Decisions, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Decisions, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  June to August
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1927-1947 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1929-1941 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1929-1941 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1929-1941 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1929-1941 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1929-1941 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Minutes re agreement and wage scale, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous reports, 1929-1931 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous reports, 1929-1931 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Financial Statement, Unemployment Fund, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous schedules, lists, notes (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous schedules, lists, notes (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Publications (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Charles F. Greenberg & Co., Inc. vs. United Infants and Children's Wear Association, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- United Infants and Children's Wear Association vs. ILGWU, 1935 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Agreement, 1934-1950 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Agreement, 1934-1950 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Agreement, 1934-1950 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Misc. re. Vacation Fund (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Jewerly Crafts Association Inc. vs. International -Jewerly Workers Union, Local 1 (IJWU), 1934 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1934-1938 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Simson Brothers Refining Corp. vs. IJWU, Local 1, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Knit Goods Industry Agreements, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Milo Knitting Mills, Inc. vs. ILGWU, Local 155, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Jewerly Crafts Association Inc. vs. IJWU, Local 1, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Baden & Foss Inc. vs. IJWU, Local 1, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Knit Goods Industry Correspondence, 1924-1944 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Propper Handbag Corp. vs. Ladles Handbag Pocketbook Workers of NY (LHPW), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Plaza Manufacturing Co. vs. Suit Case, Bag and Portfolio Makers Union, Local 60, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Nat Lewis Purses Inc. vs. LHPW, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- American Novelty Handbag Co. vs. LHPW, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Koret, Inc. vs. LHPW, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Nat Lewis Purses Inc. vs. LHPW, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Max Weinman, Inc. vs. LHPW, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Nat Lewis Purses vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Ladies Handbag Pocketbook Workers Union of NY vs. Association of NY Handbag Manufacturers, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Felder Brothers, Inc. vs. LHPW, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- William C. Rath Co. vs. International Ladies' Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union (ILHPNW), 1936 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- W. Simmons Co. vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Binnen Davis Co. vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Emes Ideal Leather Belt Co. vs. ILHPNW, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- litter and Ritter vs. LHPW, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Wollison Purses vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Lujean, Inc. vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Emes Ideal Leather Belt Co. vs. ILHPNW, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Marthalind vs. Pocketbook Workers Union, Local 1, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Jem Bag Co., Inc. vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Hamilton Novelty Co. vs. ILHPNW, Local 1, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Dofan Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- I.J. Vogel & Co. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Charles E. Block Co. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Senco Leather Manufactuers vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Rynor Bags vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Salkay Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Lewis Purses vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Mamiselle Bags, Inc. vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Dofan Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Carver Bags vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Elegant Bag Creations, vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Deutz Ltd. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry, vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Newcraft Leather Products vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Companion Bags Inc. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Harry Rosenfeld Co. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Henry Rosenfeld, Ine. vs. PWUNY, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Decor Handbag Fashions vs. PWUNY, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Rosenfeld Co. vs. PWUNY, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Dofan Handbag Co, vs. PWUNY, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Harry Rosenfeld, Inc. vs. PWUTY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Lewis Purses, Inc. vs. PWUNY, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Belt Modes, Inc. vs. Pocketbook Workers' Union of NY (PWUNY), 1945 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Doria Bag Co. vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Bello Bag vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Mercury Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Erasmus Atlas Co. vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Diana Bags vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Coronet Leather Goods Corp. vs. PWUNY, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Decker Leather Products vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- LaJulie Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Coronet, Inc. vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Gem Bag Co. vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Louis Purses vs. PWUTY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Harold and Harold vs. PWUNY, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Veterans Novelty Co. vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Buckingham Co. vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Townly Handbag, Inc. vs. PWUTY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- National Authority for the Ladies Handbag Industry vs. PWUNY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- A.J. Sirus Products Co. vs. PWUTY, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Parisian Handbags vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Solkay Bags vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Dauphin, Inc. vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Soure Bag Shop vs. PWUNY, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Leather Correspondence, 1931-1948 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1933-1949 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1933-1949 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Correspondences, 1935-1936 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1934-1936 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- J. Klotz & Co. vs. Suit Case, Bag and Portfolio Makers Union, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- J. Klotz & Co, vs. Suit Case, Bag and Portfolio Makers Union, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- United Luggage Co. vs. Suit Case, Bag and Portfolio Makers' Union, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- M & M Bag and Suit Case Co. vs. Suit Case, Bag and Portfolio Makers Union, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- S. Finkelstein & Son vs. Its Employees (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Epstein, Douglas Co. vs. Its Employees (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Harry Berger Shirt Co. vs. Two of Its Employees, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Chicago Clothing Market. Digest of Trade Board Decisions (Numbers 1-1000) and Board of Arbitration Decisions, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1913-1929 (Box 47, Folder 11)